<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Stacked Turtles - Calculators</title><link href="https://kiwidamien.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://kiwidamien.github.io/feeds/calculators.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://kiwidamien.github.io/</id><updated>2017-03-10T11:00:00-08:00</updated><entry><title>A/B Test simulator</title><link href="https://kiwidamien.github.io/ab_calc/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-03-10T11:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2017-03-10T11:00:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Damien Martin</name></author><id>tag:kiwidamien.github.io,2017-03-10:/ab_calc/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Determine the sample size needed to discover differences between two treatments, given your tolerance for false acceptances of inferior treatments, and false rejection of good treatments. Also includes a simulation of a trial, so that you can see an example of what the experimental results could look like with the given sample size.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;An A/B sample size calculator and simulator&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This post leads to (yet another) online calculator for determining the sample size needed to reliably find an effect when testing two different "treatments". These treatments could be different layouts on a website, different drugs in a trial, different teaching methodologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike many other calculators, this one will run a simulation and ask you to decide on a course of action &amp;mdash; accept or reject the alternative treatment &amp;mdash; as well as offering you feedback on the decision that you made. This approach of using simulated data gives a better understanding of Type I and Type II errors, without ruining the data from expensive experiments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
&lt;!--
            function Redirect() {
               window.location="https://kiwidamien.github.io/ab_calc/" ;
            }
         //--&gt;
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are not redirected automatically, please visit &lt;a href="https://kiwidamien.github.io/ab_calc"&gt;https://kiwidamien.github.io/ab_calc/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="A/B test"></category><category term="test"></category><category term="data"></category><category term="simulation"></category></entry></feed>